http://www.frazercomputing.com/privacypolicy

We Protect Your Personal Information
Privacy Policy:
At Frazer Computing we truly appreciate every opportunity our customers give us to assist them in achieving their goals. We want you to know that your privacy is important to us.We provide this notice to inform you how we may use non-public personal information about you or your account (private information). This notice applies to both current and former customers of Frazer Computing, Inc.We collect private information about you from the following sources:Information we receive from you, which may include your name and address.Information about your transactions with us or others, such as your payment history.Disclosure of Private Information:We may disclose your private information to the following parties:Frazer will often provide prospective dealers with a list of active Frazer customers in their area. If the prospective customer is in your area Frazer will include your name unless you request that we do not.From time to time Frazer adds new features to the software that use the services of third party companies. These companies will sometimes contact you to tell you the wonders of this new feature. We give these companies your contact information allowing them to contact you unless you request that we do not.We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. If you would like to opt-out please send an email to privacy@frazer.com . Make sure to type “Opt-Out” as the subject line or just give us a call at 1-888-963-5369.Protection of Information:We restrict access to non-public personal information about you to only those Frazer Computing employees who need this information to provide products or services to you. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.How You Can Access or Correct Your Information:You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting Frazer Computing at privacy@frazer.com. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.How to Contact Us:Should you have other questions or concerns about the Frazer Computing Privacy Policy, please call us at 1-888-963-5369 or email us at privacy@frazer.com.
Contact Us
Request A Frazer Demo
Help Desk
Copyright © 2006 - 2020 Frazer Computing, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Copyright © 2006 - 2020 Frazer Computing, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Careers
Privacy Policy
Site Map
Release Notes
